suncountry.com 2016-05-07

# Privacy

**Sun Country Privacy Statement**  

**We promise to respect your privacy.**  
As a user of the Sun Country website, you are asked to provide us with some personal information when filling out your travel profile. This information is used primarily for the purpose of learning your travel needs, preferences and requirements. The more information you provide, the more we can personalize our content and services to meet your individual needs.  

Your Ufly Rewards account number and PIN are your personal key to modifying your travel profile and providing us with your travel preferences. Before completing your personal profile, please view and accept the Terms and Conditions of using Sun Country's web site.  

**Sun Country and Secure Flight.**  
Secure Flight is a program developed to provide uniform watch list matching by the Transportation Security Administration (TSA). The mission of the Secure Flight program is to enhance the security of domestic and international commercial air travel through the use of improved watch list matching to identify known and suspected terrorists. Under the Secure Flight program, passengers will be required to provide full name (as it appears on passenger’s government-issued ID), date of birth and gender under the authority of 49 U.S.C. section 114, the Intelligence Reform and Terrorism Prevention Act of 2004 and 49 C.F.R parts 1540 and 1560. You may also provide your DHS Redress Number, if available. Sun Country will send the information you provide to the TSA where they will match it against the No Fly and Selectee watch lists. TSA may share the information you provide with law enforcement, intelligence agencies or others under its published system of records notice. By providing this information in advance, most passengers will not experience any differences from the way they traveled before as a result of Secure Flight.  

Secure Flight provides numerous benefits to the traveling public. First, Secure Flight protects sensitive watch list data. The program also enables officials to address security threats sooner, keeping air travel safer. By implementing one watch list matching system, the program provides a fair and consistent matching process across all airlines and reduces the chance of being misidentified. Secure Flight offers an improved redress process, so that those who are mistakenly matched to the watch list can avoid further problems in the future.  

The privacy of individuals’ information is a cornerstone of Secure Flight. TSA collects the minimum amount of personal information necessary to conduct effective watch list matching. Furthermore, personal data is collected, used, distributed, stored, and disposed of in accordance with stringent guidelines and all applicable privacy laws and regulations.  

For more information on Secure Flight, [click here](https://www.tsa.gov/stakeholders/secure-flight-program).  

**Cookies make your life convenient.**  
Many websites, including Sun Country, use cookie technology to help customers navigate more efficiently. The cookie is a small text file that resides on your hard drive. From time to time, our site will request the cookie from your browser so that we can retrieve the stored information. This prevents you from making the same selections over and over again. Knowing how you use the site enables us to better tailor our content and services to most effectively suit your needs. Sun Country never uses cookies to store personal information, such as credit-card numbers, nor can the information we store in the cookie ever be read by any website other than ours.  

**Shopping at Sun Country is safe and secure.**  
When you visit Sun Country's website for travel, we protect you with state-of-the-art Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, which is utilized by most popular browsers, including Netscape and Microsoft Explorer. This technology provides the advanced encryption tools necessary to protect information transmitted between your computer and our server. Encryption simply means that your information is converted into code before it is dispatched over the Internet.  

In addition to SSL technology: Your personal travel profile is PIN-protected, and it is our policy to never buy or sell this information to or from any third parties without your permission. Our secure server encrypts all personal information, including your name, address, and credit-card information; so that it cannot be read as it is transmitted over the Internet.  

We do not store your credit card information in our database. We only have access to this information when you provide it during a transaction. While we store no credit card information in our databases or on our servers, we understand that your personal information is very sensitive. To further protect the information you share with us, we have an exhaustive security system, which includes: world-class firewall technologies; logical network segmentation (allowing restricted access to stored profile information); and logical and physical security restrictions to our databases and systems.  

**Your information, your choice.**  
Sun Country takes your privacy concerns seriously and will not share your personal information without your permission. 

Once you complete a travel profile and become a member, we will occasionally use your mailing address and e-mail address to send correspondence about Sun Country including: 

  * Reservation confirmations 
  * Updates or changes to your travel plans 
  * Travel reminders - (e.g. web check-in) 
  * Requested newsletters and travel deals 
  * Special discount and/or promotional offers  

**Sun Country Airlines reserves the right to send occasional customer service e-mails to individuals that have not registered for our promotional emails.**  

Sun Country will not disclose or sell any of your personal information, including your name, address, credit-card number, shopping or transaction history to any third party other than for those purposes mentioned above. 

**Sun Country Airlines Promotional Emails**

If you have subscribed to any of our promotional emails Sun Country Airlines will not disclose or sell any of your information.  

_Please note:_ If you wish to unsubscribe from our promotional email lists, you may do so by selecting "Update Profile" at the bottom of the most recent email you have received from Sun Country Airlines.
